[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "POS", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "Anything yet?", "question_tokens": ["Anything", "yet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "We don't know what's there.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "'s", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "And Nic, given all what you've found out there, I mean is it -- is it credible that no one at any high government level or military level in Pakistan had a clue that bin Laden was in this compound?", "question_tokens": ["And", "Nic", ",", "given", "all", "what", "you", "'ve", "found", "out", "there", ",", "I", "mean", "is", "it", "--", "is", "it", "credible", "that", "no", "one", "at", "any", "high", "government", "level", "or", "military", "level", "in", "Pakistan", "had", "a", "clue", "that", "bin", "Laden", "was", "in", "this", "compound", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "VBN", "DT", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "You know I think the best clues that we have come from the neighbors.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "I", "think", "the", "best", "clues", "that", "we", "have", "come", "from", "the", "neighbors", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Pakistan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "When you saw the detail of this operation, what were your thoughts?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "saw", "the", "detail", "of", "this", "operation", ",", "what", "were", "your", "thoughts", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Well, you know, obviously, I was elated the SEALs, you know, were involved, and at the pointy edge, but also, you know, I look at it and I understand it's a team effort.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "obviously", ",", "I", "was", "elated", "the", "SEALs", ",", "you", "know", ",", "were", "involved", ",", "and", "at", "the", "pointy", "edge", ",", "but", "also", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "look", "at", "it", "and", "I", "understand", "it", "'s", "a", "team", "effort", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "I mean do you care either way?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "do", "you", "care", "either", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "Well, these guys are pros.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "these", "guys", "are", "pros", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "But from your point of view, is this the stuff that you train for?", "question_tokens": ["But", "from", "your", "point", "of", "view", ",", "is", "this", "the", "stuff", "that", "you", "train", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "Would it have bothered you in that situation whether he was armed or not?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "it", "have", "bothered", "you", "in", "that", "situation", "whether", "he", "was", "armed", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "It wouldn't have bothered me a bit, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "would", "n't", "have", "bothered", "me", "a", "bit", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "Why are they special?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "they", "special", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "Well, just look at the basic training.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "just", "look", "at", "the", "basic", "training", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ryan"]}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "RB", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "What goes through your mind?", "question_tokens": ["What", "goes", "through", "your", "mind", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "Well, you know, as Ryan had mentioned, one of the most important things, is that these guys had been trained time and time again, and so they have built up a level of inoculation to stress, so that they're able to rely on their training in those moments.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "as", "Ryan", "had", "mentioned", ",", "one", "of", "the", "most", "important", "things", ",", "is", "that", "these", "guys", "had", "been", "trained", "time", "and", "time", "again", ",", "and", "so", "they", "have", "built", "up", "a", "level", "of", "inoculation", "to", "stress", ",", "so", "that", "they", "'re", "able", "to", "rely", "on", "their", "training", "in", "those", "moments", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "Are we ever going to know who they are?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "we", "ever", "going", "to", "know", "who", "they", "are", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "Well, I hope not.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "hope", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "Is that what you would hope would happen?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "you", "would", "hope", "would", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "Well, you know, it's surprising that the numbers have remained relatively stable.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "surprising", "that", "the", "numbers", "have", "remained", "relatively", "stable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "I mean to take out bin Laden and the fact that it was a SEAL team that did this, pretty special day?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "to", "take", "out", "bin", "Laden", "and", "the", "fact", "that", "it", "was", "a", "SEAL", "team", "that", "did", "this", ",", "pretty", "special", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "NN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "It's a very special day.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "very", "special", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last several days"]}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "What is the current situation with regard to those?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "current", "situation", "with", "regard", "to", "those", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "Why, I think as we've indicated during the course of the last several days, we're making some consideration of the potential ramifications of the release of any such photos.", "answer_tokens": ["Why", ",", "I", "think", "as", "we", "'ve", "indicated", "during", "the", "course", "of", "the", "last", "several", "days", ",", "we", "'re", "making", "some", "consideration", "of", "the", "potential", "ramifications", "of", "the", "release", "of", "any", "such", "photos", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "I mean one final question with regard to the pictures, have you actually seen them yourself?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "one", "final", "question", "with", "regard", "to", "the", "pictures", ",", "have", "you", "actually", "seen", "them", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "I've seen some pictures, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "seen", "some", "pictures", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "ORGAN: And what do they depict?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "And", "what", "do", "they", "depict", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "I'm not going to get into trying to describe them.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "get", "into", "trying", "to", "describe", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "Were you able to actually see any video footage from the scene as it happened?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "able", "to", "actually", "see", "any", "video", "footage", "from", "the", "scene", "as", "it", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "No, we weren't able to see video footage from the scene.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "we", "were", "n't", "able", "to", "see", "video", "footage", "from", "the", "scene", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "Do you know if the president had spoken directly to the Navy SEALs involved in this mission yet?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "if", "the", "president", "had", "spoken", "directly", "to", "the", "Navy", "SEALs", "involved", "in", "this", "mission", "yet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "He has not yet, no.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "has", "not", "yet", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Navy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Does he plan to?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "plan", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "I anticipate he will.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "anticipate", "he", "will", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "What kind of thing would you imagine he'd say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "thing", "would", "you", "imagine", "he", "'d", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "I think they'll have an opportunity to talk directly to them.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "they", "'ll", "have", "an", "opportunity", "to", "talk", "directly", "to", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "I mean, how can you trust them after this?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "how", "can", "you", "trust", "them", "after", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "Well, it's not a matter of trust, it's a matter of finding common interests and working together with them.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "a", "matter", "of", "trust", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "matter", "of", "finding", "common", "interests", "and", "working", "together", "with", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "If Pakistan was hunting a terrorist who had killed over 3,000 of their people and they discovered after 10 years that he was residing in a compound right next to an American military base where your senior intelligence people were also working, they'd be entitled to be pretty cheesed off, wouldn't they?", "question_tokens": ["If", "Pakistan", "was", "hunting", "a", "terrorist", "who", "had", "killed", "over", "3,000", "of", "their", "people", "and", "they", "discovered", "after", "10", "years", "that", "he", "was", "residing", "in", "a", "compound", "right", "next", "to", "an", "American", "military", "base", "where", "your", "senior", "intelligence", "people", "were", "also", "working", ",", "they", "'d", "be", "entitled", "to", "be", "pretty", "cheesed", "off", ",", "would", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "RP", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "Well, it's kind of a perfect hypothetical, Piers, that I'm going to not -- I'm going to choose to not answer.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "kind", "of", "a", "perfect", "hypothetical", ",", "Piers", ",", "that", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "not", "--", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "choose", "to", "not", "answer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Pakistan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "And finally, what was your personal reaction the moment you heard that the mission was successful and bin Laden was dead?", "question_tokens": ["And", "finally", ",", "what", "was", "your", "personal", "reaction", "the", "moment", "you", "heard", "that", "the", "mission", "was", "successful", "and", "bin", "Laden", "was", "dead", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "My personal reaction was threefold.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "personal", "reaction", "was", "threefold", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ",", "CC", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "I mean I don't doubt for a moment that all those thoughts were in your mind, but I kind of hoped for a slightly more spontaneous one-liner when you heard that he was dead, something along the lines of \"got him\" or something?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "I", "do", "n't", "doubt", "for", "a", "moment", "that", "all", "those", "thoughts", "were", "in", "your", "mind", ",", "but", "I", "kind", "of", "hoped", "for", "a", "slightly", "more", "spontaneous", "one-liner", "when", "you", "heard", "that", "he", "was", "dead", ",", "something", "along", "the", "lines", "of", "``", "got", "him", "''", "or", "something", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "``", "NN", "PRP", "''", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "Well, that's exactly what the president said, but that spontaneity is not my strong suit, and spontaneity is not a big characteristic in the situation room.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "exactly", "what", "the", "president", "said", ",", "but", "that", "spontaneity", "is", "not", "my", "strong", "suit", ",", "and", "spontaneity", "is", "not", "a", "big", "characteristic", "in", "the", "situation", "room", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "Would you release them?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "release", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "This is not a major with me, but I have spoken to people who have seen the pictures.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "not", "a", "major", "with", "me", ",", "but", "I", "have", "spoken", "to", "people", "who", "have", "seen", "the", "pictures", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "I mean, it's the same thing, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "it", "'s", "the", "same", "thing", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "I agree.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "agree", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "And do you believe, if that's the case, that vindicate the case for interrogation methods like waterboarding?", "question_tokens": ["And", "do", "you", "believe", ",", "if", "that", "'s", "the", "case", ",", "that", "vindicate", "the", "case", "for", "interrogation", "methods", "like", "waterboarding", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "Let me say, first of all, I don't consider it torture.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "say", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "consider", "it", "torture", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Navy"]}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", ",", "CD", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "Would you have been perfectly happy for them to be waterboarded and put through all the other things that you think are perfectly acceptable for the people at, say, Guantanamo Bay?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "have", "been", "perfectly", "happy", "for", "them", "to", "be", "waterboarded", "and", "put", "through", "all", "the", "other", "things", "that", "you", "think", "are", "perfectly", "acceptable", "for", "the", "people", "at", ",", "say", ",", "Guantanamo", "Bay", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", ",", "VB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "Two things, one, Navy SEALS are waterboarded as part of their training.", "answer_tokens": ["Two", "things", ",", "one", ",", "Navy", "SEALS", "are", "waterboarded", "as", "part", "of", "their", "training", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Guantanamo Bay"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "So how effective is it?", "question_tokens": ["So", "how", "effective", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "ING: No, I've spoken to people on the ground, people who were involved in that.", "answer_tokens": ["ING", ":", "No", ",", "I", "'ve", "spoken", "to", "people", "on", "the", "ground", ",", "people", "who", "were", "involved", "in", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "We've always considered it torture.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'ve", "always", "considered", "it", "torture", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Yoo"]}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "I mean, President Bush insisted that he did it within the law, and that if it hadn't been deemed lawful, he wouldn't have authorized it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "President", "Bush", "insisted", "that", "he", "did", "it", "within", "the", "law", ",", "and", "that", "if", "it", "had", "n't", "been", "deemed", "lawful", ",", "he", "would", "n't", "have", "authorized", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "I think it's called plausible deniability, where John Yoo, who wrote the memo, said, look, I'm just a lawyer; I didn't make the decision.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "called", "plausible", "deniability", ",", "where", "John", "Yoo", ",", "who", "wrote", "the", "memo", ",", "said", ",", "look", ",", "I", "'m", "just", "a", "lawyer", ";", "I", "did", "n't", "make", "the", "decision", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bush"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "Where is the line drawn as far as you're concerned?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "is", "the", "line", "drawn", "as", "far", "as", "you", "'re", "concerned", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "First of all, I think waterboarding is torture.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "I", "think", "waterboarding", "is", "torture", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 400, "question": "If it works, should you use it?", "question_tokens": ["If", "it", "works", ",", "should", "you", "use", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 401, "answer": "I don't think it should be used, but I think we ought to know that we are sacrificing a great deal.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "should", "be", "used", ",", "but", "I", "think", "we", "ought", "to", "know", "that", "we", "are", "sacrificing", "a", "great", "deal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "JJ", "NNPS", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "Are you in favor of it, then, or not?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "in", "favor", "of", "it", ",", "then", ",", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "I am not in favor of it, but I understand why many Americans would favor it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "not", "in", "favor", "of", "it", ",", "but", "I", "understand", "why", "many", "Americans", "would", "favor", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Guantanamo"]}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "JJS", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNPS", ",", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "How do you get this kind of information out of implacable enemies who are prepared to dies for their cause, if you're not going to use some form of aggressive interrogation?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "get", "this", "kind", "of", "information", "out", "of", "implacable", "enemies", "who", "are", "prepared", "to", "dies", "for", "their", "cause", ",", "if", "you", "'re", "not", "going", "to", "use", "some", "form", "of", "aggressive", "interrogation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "If you bought into the last administration's argument that everyone at Guantanamo was the worst of the worst, the kind of people that would chew through the hydraulic lines of the airplane to kill Americans, then maybe waterboarding perhaps would not be considered unacceptable.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "you", "bought", "into", "the", "last", "administration", "'s", "argument", "that", "everyone", "at", "Guantanamo", "was", "the", "worst", "of", "the", "worst", ",", "the", "kind", "of", "people", "that", "would", "chew", "through", "the", "hydraulic", "lines", "of", "the", "airplane", "to", "kill", "Americans", ",", "then", "maybe", "waterboarding", "perhaps", "would", "not", "be", "considered", "unacceptable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "What do you do to get that information out of them?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "do", "to", "get", "that", "information", "out", "of", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "Well, Piers, I agree.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "agree", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "RBR", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "What I want to ask you both very quickly -- let me start with you, colonel, should we publish the picture of a dead Osama bin Laden?", "question_tokens": ["What", "I", "want", "to", "ask", "you", "both", "very", "quickly", "--", "let", "me", "start", "with", "you", ",", "colonel", ",", "should", "we", "publish", "the", "picture", "of", "a", "dead", "Osama", "bin", "Laden", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "RB", ":", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "I don't -- as someone mentioned earlier, I don't think there's any debate about the fact that he's dead.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "--", "as", "someone", "mentioned", "earlier", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "there", "'s", "any", "debate", "about", "the", "fact", "that", "he", "'s", "dead", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Osama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "Well, he's gotten a measure of credit, which he deserves.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "'s", "gotten", "a", "measure", "of", "credit", ",", "which", "he", "deserves", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "VBG", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "What's your gut feeling request?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "gut", "feeling", "request", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "The flip side of the commander in chief making the decision that he did, and being rightly credited for it, is that that decision was predicated on policies that he reviled.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "flip", "side", "of", "the", "commander", "in", "chief", "making", "the", "decision", "that", "he", "did", ",", "and", "being", "rightly", "credited", "for", "it", ",", "is", "that", "that", "decision", "was", "predicated", "on", "policies", "that", "he", "reviled", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]